Contact

snehi04@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/snehika-pandey-a15b37198 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Troubleshooting
Business Analysis
Tableau

Certifications

Matlab -Machine Learning Onramp Simulink Onramp - Matlab Matlab - Deep Learning Onramp Matlab

Snehika Pandey

Aspiring Data Scientist || Data Science Graduate Student Washington DC-Baltimore Area

Summary

I am a Data Science Graduate Student at UMBC, Maryland. I like studying and solving Data Problems.

I started as a troubleshooting engineer and then worked as a BA. I like cleaning, visualizing and modelling i.e building end to end data pipeline.

Experience

Boston Scientific Information Technology Intern May 2019 - August 2019 (4 months)

Greater Minneapolis-St. Paul Area

- Bot Development using Robotic Process Automation
- Business Test Scripts Execution, Updating and Appending During Module Creation and Up-gradation

Genpact

Business Analyst January 2018 - July 2018 (7 months) Gurgaon, India

- Conducted Product focused Business Research and Data agglomeration
- Development of Factoring and Monitoring Tool

HCL Technologies (Infrastructure Services Division) Senior Analyst

June 2015 - December 2017 (2 years 7 months)

Noida Area, India

- Capturing Event and Alert generation using Probes of Nimsoft
- Patch Scheduling and monitoring and Admin level controlling using Control-
- Daily Reporting and Server Patching, Troubleshooting and Probe Discovery for effective event capturing

Education

University of Maryland Baltimore County Master's degree, Data Science · (2018 - 2021)

DR. K.N. MODI INSTITUTE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY, MODINAGAR, GHAZIABAD Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2011 - 2015)